Guide to the Tamiment Library Newspapers PERIODICALS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- B
  - The Beacon for NMU Solidarity Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: NMU Militant-Solidarity Caucus, 1968-1979 (Box 37)
  - Because People Matter Place of publication: Sacramento, Calif. Publisher: Sacramento Community for Peace & Justice, 2002 (Box 36)
  - The Bell Wringer Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Members for a Democratic Union, 1986-1992 (Box 37)
  - Bentre Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: NYU Liberation Front, 1970-1971 (Box 37)
  - Berkeley Barb Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Scherr, Max, 1965-1979 (Box 37)
  - Berkeley Daily Planet Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Ron Mix, 1999 (Box 37)
  - The Berkeley Tribe Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Red Mountain Tribe, 1969-1972 (Box 432-433)
  - Big Mama Rag Place of publication: Denver, Colo., 1974?-1979 (Box 33)
  - Big Muddy Gazette Place of publication: Carbondale, Ill. Publisher: Muddy Tribe and Friends, 1971 (Box 84)
  - The Big Us Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio Place of publication: Cleveland Movement, 1968 (Box 34)
  - The Black Dwarf Place of publication: London, England, 1968-1970 (Box 39)
  - Black Liberation Month News Place of publication: Chicago, Ill.. Publisher: Organizing Committee for a New African Liberation Support Committee, 1978-1985 (Box 46)
  - The Black Liberator Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Black Liberation Alliance, 1969-1970? (Box 38)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7001 and Film R-7210)
  - Black Newark Place of publication: Newark, N.J. Publisher: Black People of Newark, 1968-1973 (Box 39)
  - Black Panther Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Black Panther Party, Ministry of Information, 1967-1976 (Box 38)
  - Black Panther Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Black Panther Newspaper Committee, 1991-1995 (Box 38)
  - Black Rap Place of publication: Lake Forest, Ill. Publisher: Black Students for Black Action at Lake Forest College, 1970-1973 (Box 41)
  - Black Star Place of publication: Flagstaff, Ariz. Publisher: Black Star, 1985-1987 (Box 41)
  - Black Unity Place of publication: Vista, Calif. Publisher: Black Unity, 1961-1975 (Box 161)
  - The Black Voice, 1972 (Box 38)
  - The Black Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Black Workers Council, 1971 (Box 357)
  - Black Workers Forum: Theoretical Journal of the Democratic Workers Party Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Synthesis Publications, 1981-1982 (Box 39)
  - Blind Justice Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Lawyers Guild, New York City Chapter, 1978-1981 (Box 177A)
  - BME Marine Engineer Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Brotherhood of Marine Engineers, AFL-CIO, 1956-1959 (Box 40)
  - BMWE Journal / The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Brotherhood of Maintenance Way Employees, 1996-2003 (Box 39)
  - Boilermaker Reporter Place of publication: Kansas City, Kan. Publisher: Boilermakers' Publications, 1990-current (Box 44-44A)
  - Boilermakers-Blacksmiths' Journal Place of publication: Kansas City, Kan. Publisher: International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, 1963-1989 (Box 41-43)
  - Bolshevik Place of publication: Bronx, N.Y. Publisher: Puerto Rican Revolutionary Workers Organization, 1976-1978 (Box 45)
  - Bolshevik Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Comite Central de la Ligue Trotskyste de France, 1999-2000 (Box 45)
  - The Bond Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Committee for GI Rights, 1969-1974 (Box 161)
  - Booktab Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Booktab, Inc., 1942-1943 (Box 46)
  - Bragg Briefs Place of publication: Spring Lake, N.C. Publisher: GI's United Against the War in Vietnam, 1969-1975 (Box 161)
  - Bread, Peace, and Land Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio Publisher: Independent Community Voice, 1971-1972 (Box 46)
  - British Columbia Monthly, 1972-1972 (Box 471)
  - British Workman Place of publication: London, England Publisher: S. W. Partridge, 1872 (Box 205)
  - Broadside Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Peace and Freedom Council of Los Angeles, 1968 (Box 325)
  - Broadside and the Free Press Place of publication: Cambridge, Mass. Publisher: Broadside Publications, 1969 (Box 46)
  - Broadway Local Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1971 (Box 46)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y., 1972-1973 (Box 46)
  - Brooklyn Heights Press Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Brooklyn Heights Press, 1957 (Box 46)
  - The Brooklyn Longshoreman Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: International Longshoremen's Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1814, 1964 (Box 46)
  - Brooklyn Socialist Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Socialist Party, Kings Co., 1911-1912 (Box 46)
  - Brother: Male Liberation Newspaper Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: The Brother Collective, 1971-1975 (Box 46)
  - Build the Nationwide Unemployed League Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Front Committee to Build the Nationwide Unemployed League, 1975 (Box 46)
  - The Bullet Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Mary Washington College, 1970 (Box 46)
  - Bulletin Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: National Treasury Employees Union, 1977-1980 (Box 67)
  - Bulletin / Consumers' League of New Jersey Place of publication: Newark, N.J. Publisher: Consumers' League of New Jersey, 1928-1931 (Box 46)
  - Bulletin / Consumers League of New York Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Consumers League of New York, 1925 (Box 46)
  - Bulletin: Bi-weekly Organ of the Workers League Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Workers League, 1964-1973 (Box 49-51)
  - Bulletin: Twice Weekly Organ of the Central Committee of the Workers League Place of publication:Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Labor Publications, 1973-1990 (Box 51-64)
  - Bulletin of the New York Teachers Guild Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Teachers Guild, 1935-1960 (Box 65-66)
  - The Burning Spear Place of publication: St. Petersburg, Fla. Publisher: African People's Socialist Party, 1969-2004 (Box 46A-48)
  - Butte Socialist Place of publication: Butte, Mont. Publisher: Socialist Party County Committee, 1915 (Box 70)
  - By Any Mans Necessary Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Ruchell Magee Defense Committee, nd (Box 70)
- C
  - C.N.T.: órgano de la Confederacíon Nacional del Trabajo Place of publication: Barcelona, Spain Publisher: Confederación Nacional del Trabajo, 1977-1978 (Box 27)
  - Cable Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Sales Division 18, C.W.A., 1950 (Box 115C)
  - Cable Rack Place of publication: Atlanta, Ga. Publisher: Southern Local 3290, Communications Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1969-1975 (Box 115C)
  - Cable Workers of Atlanta Local 3263 Place of publication: Norcross, Ga. Publisher: CWA Local 3263, 1984-1985 (Box 115C)
  - Cafeteria Call Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Cafeteria Employees Union, Local 302, HREBIU, AFL-CIO, 1950 (Box 74)
  - Cahiers de Mai, 1968 (Box 43)
  - California AFT Teacher Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: California Federation of Teachers, 1970-1971 (Box 74)
  - California Prisoner Place of publication: Sacramento, Calif. Publisher: Prisoners Rights Union, 1983-1998 (Box 77)
  - California Socialist Place of publication: Calif., 1981-1982 (Box 74)
  - The Call Place of publication: Bell Gardens, Calif. Publisher: The October League (M-L); Communist Party (Marxist-Leninist) (United States), 1972-1980 (Box 74-76)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    The following issues were donated by John Henle in January of 2016 and incorporated into the run of this publication: Volume 4, Number 3; Volume 5, Numbers 6, 11, 14, 19-21. The accession number associated with this gift is 2016.016.
  - Camden Tenant Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Camden Federation of Tenants and Residents Associations, 1972-1975 (Box 77)
  - Camp News Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Chicago Area Military Project, 1970-1973 (Box 162)
  - Canadian Transport Place of publication: Ottawa, Canada Publisher: Canadian Brotherhood of Railway, Transport, and General Workers, 1994 (Box 78)
  - Canadian Tribune Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: Canadian Tribune Publishing Ass., 1977-1992 (Box 78-83)
  - Canadian Worker Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: Canadian Party of Labour, 1972 (Box 84)
  - Canyon Collective Place of publication: Canyon, Calif., nd (Box 84)
  - Capitalist Reporter Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Capitalist Reporter INC., 1971-1972 (Box 84)
  - Capitol Notes / National Association of Letter Carriers Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: National Association of Letter Carriers, 1980-1984 (Box 84)
  - Career / United Office and Professional Workers of America Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), 1949 (Box 84)
  - The Carolina Plain Dealer Place of publication: U.S.A., 1970-1972 (Box 84)
  - The Carpenter Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: District Council of Carpenters, 1989-1997 (Box 77)
  - Carpetbag Express Place of publication: U.S.A., 1972 (Box 84)
  - Catholic Agitator Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Los Angeles Catholic Worker, 1980-2001 (Box 84)
  - Catholic Radical Place of publication: Milwaukee, Wis. Publisher: Casa Maria Community, 1968 (Box 84)
  - The Catholic Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: D. Day, 1997-current (Box 084A)
  - Catonsville Roadrunner Publisher: Manchester 21, 1972 (Box 84)
  - La Cause du Peuple Publisher: France, 1968-1969 (Box 84)
  - CCNY Messenger Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: City College of New York, 1998 (Box 111)
  - Cenit: Organo de la C.N.T.-A.I.T., Regional del Exterior: Portavoz de la C.N.T. de España Place of publication: Toulouse, 1983 (Box 84)
  - Central Pennsylvania Garment Worker Place of publication: Harrisburg, Pa. Publisher: Locals 108, 196 and 197, Northeast Dept., International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 167)
  - CFDT Syndicalisme Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Confédération française démocratique du travail, 1981-1986 (Box 86-87)
  - Challenge Place of publication: Davenport, Tex. Publisher: Quad Cities Community News Service (Box 94)
  - Challenge / Young People's Socialist League Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Young People's Socialist League, 1956-1958 (Box 94)
  - Challenge: Official Organ of the Young People's Socialist League Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: YPSL, 1958-1959 (Box 94)
  - Challenge: The Revolutionary Newspaper Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Progressive Labor Party, 1968-1987 (Box 88-93)
  - Change: A Working Woman's Newspaper Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif., 1971-1972 (Box 94)
  - Change-Links: Progressive Newspaper & Community Calendar Place of publication: North Hollywood, Calif. Publisher: Change-Links, 2004 (Box 94)
  - Changeover Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Motor City Labor League, 1971-1972 (Box 94)
  - Chartist Place of publication: London, England, 1972-1975 (Box 94)
  - The Chemical Worker Place of publication: Akron, Ohio Publisher: International Chemical Workers Union, 1977-1996 (Box 95-96)
  - Chessman II Place of publication: Columbia, S.C. Publisher: Short Times Staff, 1971 (Box 162)
  - Chicago Bridge Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Chicago Flower Journal and Fire Enterprises, Inc., 1967 (Box 97)
  - Chicago Seed Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Seed Publishing Co, Inc. Underground, 1972 (Box 97)
  - Chicago Union Teacher Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Chicago Teachers Union, Local 1-AFT, AFL-CIO, 1970-1971 (Box 97)
  - Chico News & Review Place of publication: Chico, Calif. Publisher: Chico Community Pub., Inc., 1978 (Box 97)
  - Chief Civil Service Leader Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Civil Service Employees Pub. Co., Inc., 2008-current (Box 101B)
  - Chile democrático: órgano oficial de la izquierda chilena, coordinador en el exterior Place of publication: Rome, Italy Publisher: Chile Democrático, 1974-1979 (Box 97)
  - Chile Newsletter Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Non-Intervention in Chile, 1976 (Box 97)
  - Chinook Place of publication: Denver, Colo., 1969-1971 (Box 97)
  - Christian Crusade Weekly Place of publication: Tulsa, Okla. Publisher: Christian Crusade, 1961-1972 (Box 98)
  - Le Chronic Place of publication: Roxbury, Mass. Publisher: Le Chronic, Inc., 1968 (Box 99)
  - Chutzpah Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Chutzpah Collective, 1972-1978 (Box 98)
  - Cine Vue: A Publication of Asian CineVision Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Asian CineVision, Inc., 1986-1995? (Box 99)
  - The CIO News Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Oil Workers International Union, 1942-1951 (Box 98)
  - CIO Transport Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Transport Workers Union, Local 156, CIO, 1941 (Box 98)
  - CIO Transport Worker Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Transport Workers Union, Local 156, CIO, 1941-1942 (Box 98)
  - CIR News / The Committee of Interns and Residents Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Committee of Interns and Residents, 1983-2010 (Box 85)
  - Circle Check Buyer and Labor News Place of publication: Richmond, Va. Publisher: Trades Union Circle Check Association, 1897-1897 (Box 97)
  - Citizen Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Wallace for President Committee, 1948 (Box 99)
  - Citizen Action News Place of publication: San Francisco, Ca. Publisher: Citizens Action League, 1987 (Box 99)
  - The Citizen Advocate / Massachusetts Fair Share Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: Massachusetts Fair Share, 1979-1983 (Box 98)
  - Citizens Voice Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Citizens Party of Northern California, 1981-1982 (Box 99)
  - Citizens Voice Place of publication: Indianapolis, Ind. Publisher: Citizens Party of Indiana, 1984 (Box 99)
  - Citizens Voice Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Citizens Party, San Francisco Chapter, 1981 (Box 99)
  - Citizens Voice Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Citizens Party, 1981-1983 (Box 99)
  - The City Hospital Worker: The Voice of Local 420, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), AFL-CIO Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Local 420, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), AFL-CIO, 1981-1996 (Box 98)
  - Civil Liberties Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: American Civil Liberties Union, 1966-1989 (Box 102)
  - Civil Liberties in New York Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Civil Liberties Union, 1953-1965 (Box 102)
  - Civil Service Leader Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Civil Service Publications, 1967-1970 (Box 99)
  - Clamshell Alliance News Place of publication: Seabrook, N.H. Publisher: Clamshell Alliance, 1977-1979 (Box 99)
  - Claridad (U.S. Supplement) Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Puerto Rican Socialist Party (PSP), 1972-1975 (Box 103-104)
  - Clarion Place of publication: Oxford, England Publisher: Oxford University Labour Club, 1960 (Box 98)
  - Clarion Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Professional Staff Congress CUNY, 1972-current (Box 105-106A)
  - The Clarion Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Clarion Publishing Association, 1932-1934 (Box 27)
  - Clark for President News Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Clark for President Committee, 1980 (Box 99)
  - Class Struggle Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Class Struggle League, 1970-1975 (Box 238)
  - Class Struggle Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: SPARK, 2001-2003 (Box 238)
  - Class War for the Dictatorship of the Proletariat Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1973 (Box 238)
  - CLC Today Place of publication: Ottawa, Canada Publisher: Canadian Labor Congress, 1990-1993 (Box 111)
  - Clinton News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Board of Publications of the General Organization of the De Witt Clinton Public High School, 1934-1935 (Box 74)
  - CNT: portavoz de la CNT de España en el exilio Place of publication: Toulouse, France Publisher: C.N.T., 1957-1982 (Box 27)
  - Coalition Place of publication: Scato, Calif. Publisher: The Coalition, 1972 (Box 162)
  - Coalition of New York Schoolworkers Newsletter Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Coalition of New York Schoolworkers, 1976-1977 (Box 279)
  - Coast Seamen's Journal: Official Organ of the Coast Seamen's Union of the Pacific Coast Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Coast Seamen's Union of the Pacific Coast, 1909-1918 (Box 513)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7352)
  - Cogito Place of publication: Syracuse, N.Y., 1968 (Box 281)
  - Cold Steel Place of publication: Buffalo, N.Y. Publisher: Onondaga Publishing Co., 1960-1970 (Box 107)
  - Collage Place of publication: New York, N.Y., nd-1970 (Box 107)
  - Collective Spirit Place of publication: Buffalo, N.Y. Publisher: University of Buffalo BSU and Third World Veterans Alliance, 1972 (Box 38)
  - College News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Student League of Greater New York, 1933 (Box 111)
  - The College Voice Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: College Voice, 1996-1999 (Box 111)
  - Colorado Labor Advocate Place of publication: Denver, Colo. Publisher: AFL-CIO, 1987-2011 (Box 108-110A)
  - Columbia Spectator Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Columbia University, 1968 (Box 108)
  - Columbus Free Press Place of publication: Columbus, Ohio, nd-1974 (Box 107)
  - Column Left Place of publication: Buffalo, N.Y. Publisher: Veterans Club at the University of Buffalo, 1972 (Box 107)
  - Combat Place of publication: Paris, France, 1968 (Box 107)
  - Combat Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Coalition Opposed to Medical and Biological Attack (Box 248)
  - Le Combat Syndicaliste Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Confederation Nationale du Travail, 1967-1982 (Box 27)
  - Combatiente: por la revolución mexicana al socialismo Place of publication: Mexico City, Mexico Publisher: Comite Central del Partido Popular Socialista, 1987 (Box 111)
  - Come Out Fighting: The Newspaper of the Lavender and Red Union Publisher: Lavender and Red Union (Box 107)
  - Come Out! Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Gay Liberation Front of New York, 1969-1971 (Box 107)
  - Comment: NYU's Journal of Political Ideas Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: NYU Libertarian Studies Association, 1982 (Box 107)
  - Committee Against Racism: National Report Place of publication: Storrs, Conn. Publisher: International Committee Against Racism, 1973-1974 (Box 107)
  - Committee for Prisoner Humanity and Justice Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Humanity and Justice (Box 341)
  - Committee to Support Middle East Liberation Newsletter Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Committee to Support Middle East Liberation, 1969-1971 (Box 107)
  - Common Ground Place of publication: Juneau, Alaska Publisher: Alaska Common Ground Collective, 1980-1981 (Box 107)
  - Common Sense Place of publication: Bloomington, Ind. Publisher: Bloomington Independent Publishing Corp., 1971-1972 (Box 107)
  - Common Sense Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: San Francisco Socialist Coalition, 1974 (Box 248)
  - Common Sense Place of publication: Springfield, nd (Box 107)
  - Common Sense Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Peoples Bicentennial Commission, 1974 (Box 107)
  - Common Sense: Newsmonthly of the Northern California Alliance Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Northern California Alliance, 1976 (Box 107)
  - Common Woman Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Common Woman Collective, 1971 (Box 477)
  - Commonwealth Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1919 (Box 107)
  - Commonwealth Place of publication: Regina, Canada Publisher: New Democratic Party, 1977-1989 (Box 111-113)
  - Commonwoman Place of publication: Winooski, Vt. Publisher: Commonwoman, 1978-1981 (Box 114)
  - Commonwork Pamphlets Place of publication: New Haven, Conn., nd (Box 114)
  - Communications Journal Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Communications Organizing Committee of the American Radio Telegraphists Association, 1937 (Box 115C)
  - Communications Workers of America - District 1 Hot Line Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Communications Workers of America, 1983-1997 (Box 114)
  - Communications Workers of America Local 1111 Newsletter Place of publication: Elmira, N.Y. Publisher: Communications Workers of America Local 1111, 1985-1986 (Box 115C)
  - Communicator Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York State Public Employees, 1975 (Box 114)
  - Communique Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Local 1180 CWA, 1977-current (Box 114A)
  - Communist, 1971 (Box 238)
  - Communist Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Central Committee of the Marxist-Leninist Party, 1970-1971 (Box 238)
  - Communist: Official Organ of the United Communist Party of America Place of publication:[Chicago, Ill.?] Publisher: United Communist Party of America, 1920 (Box 513)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7186)
  - Communist Line Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Marxist-Leninist Organizing Committee, 1975 (Box 114)
  - Community Press Features Place of publication: Cambridge, Mass., 1977-1981? (Box 114)
  - Compita, El Place of publication: Mexico City, Mexico Publisher: Impresos Alfa, 1982 (Box 128)
  - Connecticut Labor Gazette Place of publication: Conn. Publisher: Teamsters Joint Council 64 (Connecticut) Bricklayers, Laborers, and Ironworkers, 1972-1974 (Box 114)
  - Connections Place of publication: Madison, Wis., 1967 (Box 114)
  - Conspiracy Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Bay Area Regional Office, National Lawyers Guild, 1970-1992 (Box 113A)
  - Construction Labor News Place of publication: San Jose, Calif. Publisher: Bette Dravis, 1984 (Box 114B)
  - Contact: Essence of Life Place of publication: Conn. Publisher: Afro-American Cultural Center, 1972 (Box 38)
  - Contempo Place of publication: Chapel Hill, N.C., 1933 (Box 111)
  - Contract Countdown Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Coalition for a Good Contract, UAW, 1976 (Box 114)
  - Controborghese Publisher: Frosinone, 1968 (Box 114)
  - Convention Report Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Caucus of SDS Labor Committees, 1969 (Box 114)
  - Convoy Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio Publisher: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1976-1979 (Box 501)
  - Convoy Dispatch: Voice of Teamsters for a Democratic Union Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1979-1997 (Box 504)
  - Co-op Cornucopia Place of publication: Madison, Wis., 1979 (Box 107)
  - Cooperator Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Housing Foundation, 1967 (Box 108)
  - Coordinator Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Inter-union Coordinating Committee, 1944 (Box 115C)
  - Corpus Creator News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Sons of Light INC., 1970 (Box 115)